# **NICOLAS GABRIEL ARBIO**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CABA, Argentina (GMT-3) 

nicolasarbio@outlook.com

nicoarbio

Nicolás Gabriel Arbio

European Citizenship

## **MY PROFILE**

Passionate developer with strong coding skills and experience working in international teams from Germany, US, India and Italy among others.

Currently working as a Java Software Engineer using Scrumban.

My main stack is Java, SQL and Git with drive to learn new technologies, currently focused on mastering Spring Boot and React.JS.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER / SEP 2022 - PRESENT / ELDAR

- Responsible of migrating JAVA services using jPos framwork for a bank customer.
- Migration of JDK, Gradle wrapper, jPos + modules, Jetty, Jersey and Swagger.
- Using Oracle DB Flashback queries, service runtime was reduced from 3 hours to 5 seconds.

## SSr. SAP Basis Transformation Consultant / AGO 2019 - SEP 2022 / SNP GROUP

- SAP systems readiness for migrations (file paths, errors check, memory and CPU)
- Analysis, preparation, execution and monitoring of the transformation processes.
- VBA scripts development for the automation of reports generation in Excel about runtime analysis and system processes performance.
- Development of PowerBI portal for team resource management using Power Automate.

#### **EDUCATION**

# EduacaciónIT Argentina / 2022 - PRESENT

Courses covering: Java, SQL, Linux, Spring, Spring Boot and IT security.

## Systems Analyst | ORT Argentina / MAR 2020 - DEC 2021

- Java: Data structures, OOP and design patterns.
- Kotlin: Development of 2 apps, for a social initiative by `Ciudades del Futuro` using Fiware and Firebase.
- Node.JS: Clinical system. Management of patients, doctors and appointments.
- SQL Server: Development of store procedures and triggers.
- C# .NET Core: Development of a MVC system: `Bike Rental`.
- Scrum: Usage of roles, prioritized backlog, sprints, meetings, and create user stories.

## LANGUAGES

#### SOFT SKILLS

Spanish | English (B2)

Team Work + Problem Solving + Responsible & Goals-Oriented + Fast-Learning + Continuous Improvement + Proactivity + Empathy.

\*\*\*\*